Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Production Files
  - Subseries A: Mabou Mines stage productions
    - Sueños INTAR co-production, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 632)
    - Sueños Boston Musica Viva, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 633)
    - Sueños Boston Musica Viva "Young at Arts", 1989 (Box 14, Folder 634)
    - Sueños rights, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 635)
    - Sueños artist agreements, contracts, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 636)
    - Sueños composer research; resume, undated (Box 14, Folder 637)
    - Sueños studies for painted drops and set elements - Eduardo Carrillo [photocopies w/ bio info], 1988, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 2282)
      Set design and lighting info, PR, screenings, etc.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236169
    - Sueños lottery tickets, ca. 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2283)
    - Sueños project description, ca. 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2284)
    - Sueños costume files, 1988-1989 (Box 110, Folder 2285)
    - Sueños BMCC Triplex lighting info, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2286)
    - Sueños light cues, at The Triplex, 2/89; light cues data cassettes [2], 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2287)
    - Sueños tech specs - 20-min. concert version, ca. 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2288)
    - Sueños tech specs and lighting info, Northeastern University [incl. light templates], 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2289)
    - Sueños Northeastern University prod. files, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2290)
    - Sueños press list, ca. 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2291)
    - Sueños general files, ca. 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2292)
    - Sueños Gracie Mansion reception files, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 2293)
    - Sueños P.S. 122 prod. files, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 2294)
    - Sueños American Repertory Theatre prod. files, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2295)
    - Sueños NuArts Festival files, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2296)
    - Sueños Boston Musica Viva files, 1988 (Box 110, Folder 2297)
    - Sueños Triplex contracts, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2295)
    - Sueños Triplex financial files, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2296)
    - Sueños Triplex prod. files, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 2297)
    - Sueños general info, 1988-1989 (Box 110, Folder 2298)
    - Sueños general correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 110, Folder 2299)
    - The Warrior Ant draft with corrections and marginalia July 16, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 638)
    - The Warrior Ant at Yale [?], photos of Japanese puppet theater, undated (Box 14, Folder 639)
    - The Warrior Ant funding, budgets, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 640)
    - The Warrior Ant financial: fundraising, etc., 1989 (Box 14, Folder 641)
      includes Sueños files
    - The Warrior Ant financial, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 642)
    - The Warrior Ant set design photo, undated (Box 14, Folder 643)
    - The Warrior Ant agreements, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 644)
    - The Warrior Ant press, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 645)
    - The Warrior Ant descriptions, programs, press, undated (Box 14, Folder 646)
    - The Warrior Ant photo with sketch, by Alison Yerxa, undated (Box 14, Folder 647)
    - The Warrior Ant photographs, Eleonora Alberto, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 648)
    - The Mormon Project statement drafts, undated (Box 15, Folder 649)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235880
    - The Mormon Project info sheets: statements, bios, etc., 1989 (Box 15, Folder 650)
    - The Mormon Project Utah trip itinerary, flight info, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 651)
    - The Mormon Project NY rehearsals: budgets, schedules, contracts, notes Oct, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 652)
    - The Mormon Project budgets, contact sheets, notes, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 653)
    - The Mormon Project projected touring budgets, schedules, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 654)
    - The Mormon Project Atlantic Center for the Arts, FL, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 655)
    - The Mormon Project Center Arts, Humboldt State Univerisity, CA, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 656)
    - The Mormon Project Red Eye Collaboration, Minneapolis, MN, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 657)
    - The Mormon Project residencies/co-production inquiries, 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 658)
    - The Mormon Project Actors' Equity contracts, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 659)
    - The Mormon Project development: grant applications, etc.; NEA, NYSCA, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 660)
    - The Mormon Project financial records: budgets, receipts, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 661)
    - The Mormon Project financial records: expenses, receipts, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 662)
    - The Mormon Project Mormon-related publications, undated (Box 15, Folder 663)
    - The Mormon Project Mormon-related books [photocopies of chapters], undated (Box 15, Folder 664)
    - The Mormon Project research materials: Mormon-related articles, etc. [photocopies], undated (Box 15, Folder 665)
    - The Mormon Project book: Sherman, Kay. The Findhorn Family Cook Book., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 666)
    - The Mormon Project JoAnne Akalaitis's notes, notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 667)
    - The Mormon Project script development, undated (Box 15, Folder 668)
    - The Mormon Project Mormon/Evangelical-related press clippings, undated (Box 15, Folder 669)
    - The Mormon Project music, Terry Allen info, undated (Box 15, Folder 670)
    - The Mormon Project Eric Overmeyer, writer, undated (Box 15, Folder 671)
    - The Mormon Project biographies, undated (Box 15, Folder 672)
    - The Mormon Project Michelle Shocked info, press, undated (Box 15, Folder 673)
    - The Mormon Project sample box office forms, undated (Box 15, Folder 674)
    - The Mormon Project performance notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 675)
    - The Mormon Project correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 676)
    - Lear budgets, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 677)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235898
    - Lear expenses, receipts, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 678)
    - Lear finances, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 679)
    - Lear finances, receipts, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 680)
    - Lear finances, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 681)
    - Lear expenses, receipts, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 682)
    - Lear receipts, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 683)
    - Lear finances, checks, payrolls, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 684)
    - Lear payroll, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 685)
    - Lear financial records, Smith College March, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 686)
    - Lear financial records, Smith College, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 687)
    - Lear financial records, Smith College, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 688)
    - Lear development, undated (Box 16, Folder 689)
    - Lear benefit at the Public Theater, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 690)
    - Lear benefits, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 691)
    - Lear benefit checks, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 692)
    - Lear loan requests, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 693)
    - Lear NEFA (New England Foundation for the Arts) reimbursements, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 694)
    - Lear NEFA reimbursements, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 695)
    - Lear box office statements, settlements Jan-Feb, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 696)
    - Lear Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 697)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235906
    - Lear New Jersey bust trip Jan, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 698)
    - Lear Storm King July, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 699)
    - Lear George Street Playhouse: press, programs, flyers, etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 700)
    - Lear George Street Playhouse, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 701)
    - Lear George Street Playhouse, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 702)
    - Lear benefit at the Public Theater Dec 12, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 703)
    - Lear Smith College: notes, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 704)
    - Lear Smith College: agreements, correspondence, travel, etc., 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 705)
    - Lear Smith College March, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 706)
    - Lear New York residency Sept-Feb, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 707)
    - Lear Triplex Theatre, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 708)
    - Lear Triplex Theatre, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 709)
    - Lear Triplex Theatre extension, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 710)
    - Lear Toronto: Carnet ("Move goods duty-free through customs."), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 711)
    - Lear Toronto: insurance info March, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 712)
    - Lear Toronto: Harborfront March, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 713)
    - Lear Toronto: Harborfront, etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 714)
    - Lear Actors' Equity contracts, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 715)
    - Lear Ardani Arts Management, re: Russia tour, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 716)
    - Lear The Lear Tapes, video documentary, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 717)
    - Lear employment records, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 718)
    - Lear bios and resumes, undated (Box 17, Folder 719)
    - Lear casting, undated (Box 17, Folder 720)
    - Lear rehearsal notes, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 721)
    - Lear preliminary sketches, groundplan, elevations, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 722)
    - Lear technical notes, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 723)
    - Lear description; Breuer personal statement, undated (Box 17, Folder 724)
    - Lear costume notes Feb, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 725)
    - Lear sound notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 726)
    - Lear press, flyers, etc., undated (Box 17, Folder 727)
      includes "Theater Week" article on Frank Rich
    - Lear contact sheets, undated (Box 17, Folder 728)
    - Lear Jonathan Atkin Photography correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 17, Folder 729)
    - Lear Pauline Oliveros, composer, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 730)
    - Lear Pauline Oliveros, press kit and correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 731)
    - Lear Arena Stage correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 732)
    - Lear 890 Dance Center, rehearsal studio rental, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 733)
    - Lear various notes, undated (Box 17, Folder 734)
    - Lear advertising, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 735)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235914
    - Lear reservations, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 736)
      includes B. Beaver Animation
    - Lear group sales, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 737)
    - Lear photos: props and scenic elements, undated (Box 18, Folder 738)
    - Lear lighting: press clippings, undated (Box 18, Folder 739)
    - Lear fight director clipping, undated (Box 18, Folder 740)
    - Lear project description, etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 741)
    - Lear props and costumes, undated (Box 18, Folder 742)
    - Lear golf carts/Dennis Gronim, 1988-1991 (Box 18, Folder 743)
    - Lear props: car ideas, undated (Box 18, Folder 744)
    - Lear props, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 745)
    - Lear Lear/Phaedra notes, contact sheets, etc., undated (Box 18, Folder 746)
    - Lear program book original, undated (Box 18, Folder 747)
    - Lear correspondence: instructions on Shakespearean scansion, undated (Box 18, Folder 748)
    - Lear correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 18, Folder 749)
    - Lear electrics: Triplex Theatre hook-up, cues, Kliegl data cassette, undated (Box 18, Folder 750)
    - Lear lighting: Toronto hook-up, cues, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 751)
      see also oversize for plots
    - Lear gobo, undated (Box 18, Folder 752)
    - Lear gobos; Toronto and Wexner Center, undated (Box 18, Folder 753)
    - Lear wardrobe, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 754)
    - Lear script, with costume notes in margins, undated (Box 18, Folder 755)
    - Lear revised houses (facades), undated (Box 18, Folder 756)
    - In the Jungle of Cities project descriptions, undated (Box 18, Folder 757)
    - In the Jungle of Cities resumes, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 758)
    - In the Jungle of Cities designers: resumes, etc., 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 759)
    - In the Jungle of Cities New York: correspondence, agreements Jan, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 760)
    - In the Jungle of Cities prop list Sept, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 761)
    - In the Jungle of Cities props borrowed, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 762)
    - In the Jungle of Cities Via Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 763)
    - In the Jungle of Cities The Public Theater, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 764)
    - In the Jungle of Cities contact sheets, schedules, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 765)
    - In the Jungle of Cities general correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 766)
    - In the Jungle of Cities stage manager's reports, NY Shakespeare Festival, Public Theater Oct-Nov, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 767)
    - In the Jungle of Cities press, P.R., NY Shakespeare Festival, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 768)
    - In the Jungle of Cities Playbill proofs, NY Shakespeare Festival, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 769)
    - In the Jungle of Cities tech specs, Public Theater, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 770)
    - In the Jungle of Cities rights, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 771)
    - In the Jungle of Cities contracts, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 772)
    - In the Jungle of Cities artists' contracts, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 773)
    - In the Jungle of Cities design contracts, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 774)
    - In the Jungle of Cities tech contracts, Public Theater, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 775)
    - In the Jungle of Cities Actors' Equity info, agreements, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 776)
    - In the Jungle of Cities video, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 777)
    - In the Jungle of Cities accident reports Nov, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 778)
    - In the Jungle of Cities budgets, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 779)
    - In the Jungle of Cities expenses Oct-Nov, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 780)
    - In the Jungle of Cities box office statements, Public Theater Oct-Nov, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 781)
    - In the Jungle of Cities development: correspondence, etc., 1991 (Box 18, Folder 782)
    - In the Jungle of Cities touring packet, press, art work, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 783)
    - In the Jungle of Cities promotional photos, artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 784)
    - In the Jungle of Cities touring information, correspondence May-Aug, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 785)
    - In the Jungle of Cities touring budgets, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 786)
    - In the Jungle of Cities interns, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 787)
    - In the Jungle of Cities Mario Arrambide: bio, headshot, resume, reviews, undated (Box 18, Folder 788)
    - In the Jungle of Cities original artwork, undated (Box 18, Folder 789)
    - The Bribe "Illusion" card, photocopies, undated (Box 19, Folder 790)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235922
    - The Bribe "I'm Deaf" card, original, undated (Box 19, Folder 791)
    - The Bribe artistic statements, undated (Box 19, Folder 792)
    - The Bribe press release, info, clippings, undated (Box 19, Folder 793)
    - The Bribe WGBH radio production, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 794)
    - The Bribe radio license agreement, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 795)
    - The Bribe artists' agreements, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 796)
    - The Bribe touring needs, undated (Box 19, Folder 797)
    - The Bribe equipment inventory April 24, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 798)
    - The Bribe passport photo; Joanna Settle, stage manager, undated (Box 19, Folder 799)
    - The Bribe resumes, undated (Box 19, Folder 800)
    - The Bribe correspondence, etc., 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 801)
    - The Bribe agreement: John Zorn, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 802)
    - The Bribe Ghent Festival, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 803)
    - The Bribe P.S. 122, undated (Box 19, Folder 804)
    - The Bribe Smith College Summer Retreat, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 805)
    - The Bribe / The MahabharANTa agreements, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 806)
    - The Bribe / The MahabharANTa Ontological at St. Mark's Fall, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 807)
    - The Bribe / The MahabharANTa Ontological at St. Mark's: program Fall, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 808)
    - The Bribe press lists, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 809)
    - The Bribe Theater for the New City: flyer original, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 810)
    - The Bribe press release, flyers, etc., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 811)
    - The Bribe Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 812)
    - The Bribe Singapore technical info, hook-ups, etc., 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 813)
    - The Bribe Singapore tech correspondence, lighting cues, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 814)
    - The Bribe Singapore lighting cue sheets, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 815)
    - The Bribe National Arts Council correspondence, re: Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 816)
    - The Bribe National Arts Council correspondence, re: Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 817)
    - The Bribe Singapore Festival of the Arts, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 818)
    - The Bribe 2nd Stage, University of Arizona West, Phoenix: lighting, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 819)
    - The Bribe 2nd Stage, University of Arizona West, Phoenix: program, notes, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 820)
    - The Bribe Australia touring contacts, undated (Box 19, Folder 821)
    - The Bribe European contacts, undated (Box 19, Folder 822)
    - The Bribe West Coast touring, undated (Box 19, Folder 823)
    - The Bribe Japanese contacts The Bribe Japanese contacts, undated (Box 19, Folder 824)
    - The Bribe inquiries, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 825)
    - The Bribe Hong Kong Arts Festival inquiries, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 826)
    - The Bribe negative replies, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 827)
    - The Bribe Saratoga Internation Theater Institute: negative reply, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 828)
    - The Bribe box office records: Theater for the New City, Ontological, etc., 1993 (Box 19, Folder 829)
    - The Bribe development, 1986-1994 (Box 19, Folder 830)
    - The Bribe budget, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 831)
    - The Bribe budget, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 832)
    - The Bribe / The MahabharANTa expenses, receipts, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 833)
    - The Bribe expenses, receipts April, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 834)
    - The MahabharANTa "The Insect Who Loved the World" correspondence, bios, press, etc., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 835)
    - The MahabharANTa notes and correspondence between company members, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 836)
    - The MahabharANTa correspondence between Larry Reed and Lee Breuer, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 837)
    - The MahabharANTa program information, undated (Box 19, Folder 838)
    - The MahabharANTa technical, undated (Box 19, Folder 839)
    - The MahabharANTa description, press release, undated (Box 19, Folder 840)
    - The MahabharANTa I Wayan Wija, Balinese puppeteer: CV, photograph, press, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 841)
    - The MahabharANTa agreements, 1985-1992 (Box 19, Folder 842)
    - The MahabharANTa St. Ann's, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 843)
    - The MahabharANTa International Festival of Puppet Theater, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 844)
    - The MahabharANTa SUNY Stonybrook, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 845)
    - The MahabharANTa Bali, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 846)
    - The MahabharANTa Arizona State University, Phoenix, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 847)
    - The MahabharANTa Tisch School of the Arts, NYU, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 848)
    - The MahabharANTa Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 849)
    - The MahabharANTa Atlanta Center for Puppetry Arts, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 850)
    - The MahabharANTa MIT, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 851)
    - The MahabharANTa correspondence, inquiries, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 852)
    - The MahabharANTa development, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 853)
    - The MahabharANTa budget: NY tour, undated (Box 19, Folder 854)
    - The MahabharANTa box office records Oct 13-Nov 16, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 855)
    - Dead End Kids light cue sheets, tracking sheets and notes (Mark Taper Forum, Dock Street Theater), ca. 1980-1984 (Box 109, Folder 2277)
      Scripts, checking account files & stubs, press, screening info, etc.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236151
    - Dead End Kids hook-up sheets, star template, groundplans, ca. 1980-1984 (Box 109, Folder 2278)
      Finances, press, resumes, screening info, mailing lists, etc.
    - Dead End Kids press, ca. 1980-1984 (Box 109, Folder 2279)
      Press, distribution info, grants, finances, etc.
    - Dead End Kids touring files, ca. 1980-1984 (Box 109, Folder 2280)
      Funding, distributioon info, film festival files, etc.
    - Dead End Kids script & notes, ca. 1981-1983 (Box 109, Folder 2281)
      Technical files, touring info, etc.
    - Reel to Real income & disbursments ledger; accounts payable journal, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2300)
      Finances, screenings, promotional material, workshop info, lighting and equipment files, grants, etc.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236177
    - Reel to Real early notes, 1990-1991 (Box 111, Folder 2301)
    - Reel to Real production files, 1991-1992 (Box 111, Folder 2302)
    - Reel to Real script development, undated (Box 111, Folder 2303)
    - Reel to Real equipment lists, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2304)
    - Reel to Real sketches for set, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2305)
    - Reel to Real The Theatre Institute at Storm King files, 1990-1991 (Box 111, Folder 2306)
    - Reel to Real flyer mock-up, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2307)
    - Reel to Real video files, 1992-1993 (Box 111, Folder 2308)
    - Reel to Real class notes, 1992 (Box 111, Folder 2309)
    - Reel to Real workshop, Arizona State University West, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2310)
    - Reel to Real workshop, Bucknell University, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2311)
    - Reel to Real The Kitchen premiere, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2312)
    - Reel to Real Duke University production files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2313)
    - Reel to Real inquiries, 1990-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2314)
    - Reel to Real biographical material, N/A (Box 111, Folder 2315)
    - Reel to Real Al Kryszak files [incl. photo and slides], 1993 (Box 111, Folder 2316)
    - Reel to Real New York University files, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 2317)
    - Reel to Real Yellow Springs Institute files, 1992-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2318)
    - Reel to Real touring files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2319)
    - Reel to Real correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2320)
    - Reel to Real NYSCA film application files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2321)
    - Reel to Real development files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2322)
    - Reel to Real film financial files, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2323)
    - Reel to Real ASU West fincancial files, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 2324)
    - Reel to Real Bucknell University financial files, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2325)
    - Reel to Real The Kitchen financial files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2326)
    - Reel to Real financial files, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2327)
    - Reel to Real financial files, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 2328)
    - Animal Magnetism scripts [drafts] w/ related project notes and misc. files, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 2329)
    - Benefits - committee mailing lists, 1982-1985 (Box 112, Folder 2330)
      Incl. files for benefits, Grey Art Gallery, Animal Magnetism, and Lear.
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042236185
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit - individual donors, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 2331)
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit - thank yous, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 2332)
    - 15th Anniversary Benefit files, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 2333)
    - Benefit files, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 2334)
    - Benefit budgets, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 2335)
    - Beckett Benefit files, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 2336)
    - Friends Seminary Benefit, 1988 (Box 112, Folder 2337)
    - 20th Anniversary promotional material, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 2338)
    - 20th Anniversary info, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 2339)
    - 20th Anniversary - Grey Art Gallery checklist, plans and report, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 2340)
    - 20th Anniversary - Grey Art Gallery press, 1990 (Box 112, Folder 2341)
    - Indonesia Benefit, 1992-1993 (Box 112, Folder 2342)
    - Misc. unidentified set effects slides, undated (Box 112, Folder 2373)
  - Subseries B: Mabou Mines artist-in-residence programs
    Files from productions of Re-Cher-Chez, a studio for avant-garde performing arts, and Mabou Mines/Suite, the company's artists-in-residence/theater training program.
    - Re-Cher-Chez grant applications, descriptions, bios, press, budgets, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 856)
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042235930
    - Re-Cher-Chez announcements, programs, photos, contact sheets, 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 857)
    - Re-Cher-Chez statement by Lisa Lorwin Aug 28, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 858)
    - Re-Cher-Chez photos: Mayfest, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 859)
    - Mabou Mines/Suite press release, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 860)